Contact

trinirn40@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/natashahyde-46a4229b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Management Clinical Research Hospitals

Natasha Hyde

Director Patient Care Med/Surg and PT/OT Services at CHI St. Luke's Health

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Unit Director with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Physician Relations, Healthcare Management, Healthcare, Clinical Research, and Patient Safety. Strong business development professional with a MSN focused in Nursing Education from Walden University.

Experience

CHI St. Luke's Health
Director Patient Care Med/Surg
2019 - Present (1 year)
Sugarland, Texas

Houston Methodist
Manager/Director
September 2015 - August 2019 (4 years)
Houston, Texas Area

Grady Health System
Unit Director Surgical Trauma
August 2014 - September 2015 (1 year 2 months)
Atlanta

Atlanta Medical Center

Nurse Manager

July 2012 - July 2014 (2 years 1 month)

Education

New York University
Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing

Walden University

MSN, Nursing Education